http://www.fastrology.co.uk/privacy

Fastrology Privacy Policy Statement
This Privacy Policy Statement explains the data processing practices
of www.fastrology.co.uk. If you have any requests concerning your personal
information or any queries with regard to these practices please
contact our Privacy Officer by e-mail via our online form
Eligibility
This service is open to anyone based in the UK who is over the age of 18.
Registration & Information Collected
We collect personal information from you through the use of enquiry
and registration forms and each time you e-mail us your details.
We also collect information automatically about your visit to our
site. This information, which includes demographic data and
browsing patterns, is collected via the use of cookies (see below)
and session file information.
Use of personal information
We use personal information collected via www.fastrology.co.uk to:
provide you with information about the products and services we offer
provide you with a more personalised service
conduct market research
run competitions and promotions
pass on to selected companies to provide you with other offers and promotions
help other companies profile and extend their databases
facilitate communication between yourself and others
Allow us to send you, via e-mail, telephone, SMS and post, special offers and promotions from prize sponsors and promoters including but not limited to Marketing Craze Ltd and Premium Genie.
provide third party offers which may include premium rate SMS and telephone charges. Check terms for details and obtain permission from the bill payer before using these services.
We currently only keep "sensitive data", as defined by the Data
Protection Act 1998 for the explicit purpose of providing initial
and renewal car insurance quotations.
Use of cookies
Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit
www.aboutcookies.org
.
Below is a table of cookies placed by data media and research on your computer, and their purpose.
Cookie
Name
Purpose
More information
Google Analytics
_utma_utmb_utmc_utmz
These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where vistors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.
Click here for an overview of privacy at Google
PHP session cookie
PHPSESSID
This cookie is used to preserve certain data across subsequent accesses. This enables us to build more customized applications and increase the functionality of our web site.
Click here for more information about PHP Sessions
Use of session files
We use session files, along with cookies, to log your browsing
patterns and so identify the areas of the site which have been of
interest to you, allowing us to personalise the www.fastrology.co.uk site for
you.
We also use information in aggregate form (in other words, no
individual user is identified) to:
build up marketing profiles
allow us to develop the business in ways that help you
manage our relationship with advertisers and
audit usage of the site.
All personal, cookie and session ID information are made
available to www.fastrology.co.uk call centre employees to enable us and any
related third parties to deal more effectively with any enquiry you
make.
Your control over the use of your personal data
You have complete control over the use of your personal information
by www.fastrology.co.uk.
We want the opportunity to make you offers and unless you are
willing to agree to this you can't complete the surveys.
However this permission can be revoked at any time through your
account page or via an email unsubscribe link.
If you do
decide to revoke it, then survey entries already made
will remain in force.
Consent to the transfer of your personal data to service
providers acting for DMR who may be based outside the EEA and that
DMR will take all reasonable required steps to ensure that your data and
privacy rights continue to be protected
No data will be retained through the use of the "refer a friend" mechanism
other than to notify the friend until that friend then decides to join and
register with the site
Our site links to other web sites and we are not responsible for
their data policies and procedures.
Security
We use 128 bit encryption technology for the transmission from you
to us of financially sensitive data, i.e. credit card details, but
cannot guarantee the security of any data you send to us.
Data Protection
www.fastrology.co.uk is wholly owned by Data Media and Research Limited, which is registered
